C'est-à-dire que quand le CV1, il va trouver le canal vide. Il va croire que le canal que le B il n'est pas occupé. Alors que B il est en train d'occu d'être de recevoir les données de l'A.
That is, when CV1, it will find the channel empty. He will believe that the channel that the B he is not occupied. While B is in the process of receiving data from A.
الو و الربطة تاع الإنتهاء ماشي، ها تنتمي.  [noise]  Je répète. [noise]  On suppose que غادي نقولها لكم و [unintelligible] و [unintelligible] parce que [unintelligible].
Hello and the end tie is fine, it belongs here.  [noise]  Je répète. [noise]  On suppose que Gadi we say it to you and [unintelligible] and [unintelligible] parce que [unintelligible].
hmouri fiha mniha fil maison. Alors, chouf, l'a est en train de transmettre la B. Si, hams, [noise]
Hmouri Fiha Mniha Wire House. So, chouf, the a is transmitting the B. Si, hams, [noise]
asses the the color. It's the color. Vous pouvez que le canal, il est vide. Il n'ont rien parce que le rien, je dirais le A, il n'englobe pas le C.
asses the the color. It's the color. You can that the channel, it is empty. They have nothing because nothing, I would say A, it does not include C.
if we start sending data to B. At this moment, B is receiving data from A.
collision happen happened at B. We are going to call A. [unintelligible] terminal for C. [unintelligible] terminal. [unintelligible] problem.
راها كراشي. و.  هذا يهدر مع مع علي.  هذه الهدره تاع علي ما وصلتش لحقني باسكو بعيد عليها.
See her Karashi. And. This is talking with Ali.  This talk of Ali didn't reach follow me Pasco away from it.
نحسب اللي علي دي ليبر يا با با دو يا با دو [unintelligible] [unintelligible] راهم يهضروش. شو راك مور الباب مور الباب يحسب
We count that Ali de Liber or Ba Ba Do or Ba Do [unintelligible] [unintelligible] they will be destroyed. What do you see more the door more the door counts
علي [unintelligible] علي. [unintelligible] [unintelligible] parce que علي [unintelligible] communication [unintelligible] avec علي. [noise]
علي [unintelligible] علي. [unintelligible] [unintelligible] because علي [unintelligible] communication [unintelligible] with علي. [noise]
Voilà, donc sur ce donc je vous demanderai de réfléchir à ça. Ah, au compte déjà comprendre, super. Voilà. [unintelligible] dans la collision sera  à B ou là à A. [unintelligible]
So there you go, so on that so I'll ask you to think about that. Ah, on the count already understand, great. There you go. [unintelligible] in the collision will be at B or there at A. [unintelligible]
عندك باي، سي، سي باي يهضر مع البي، كيبعث لدوني للبي، والار يهضر مع البي، والار ديجا يهضر مع البي. م، عط، وديجا سي ميغاتش كومنيكي مع الار، شو؟
You have Bye, C, and C-bay that is harmful to the B, that the Lib send to the Lib, that the Lar is the Lib, and that the R Dega is the Lib. M, Atta, and Dega C Mega Komniki with the AR, what?
راش ما يوصلش للآ. وي فاش ما يوصلش للآ. فهمت؟  واه فهمت. هذا هو البروبلم نتاع التيمينال كاش. الخطرة الجاية نعاود نديرو ان اكزرسيس عليه ونحكي لكم على التيمينال اكسبوز.
Rush doesn't get to No. Wei Fash doesn't reach now. Do you understand?  Oh, I get it. This is the terminal cash prop. Next danger, we're going to do it again and we're going to tell you about the terminal exposure.
Je vous remercie, je vous dis donc euh sans m'échauffer, je. Euh les tests on va faire le
Thank you, I say to you so uh without warming up, I. Uh, the tests, we're going to do the
le le premier et le deux. Donc choisir une séance pour le premier ou deux, hein, d'accord.
the first and the two. So choose a session for the first one or two, eh, okay.
يسمى [unintelligible] بعدكم باش تفهمو على لاسونس. يا سلام عليكم.
It is called [unintelligible] after you understand on Lassons. Oh peace be upon you.
وعليكم السلام.
Peace be upon you.